>> Jem Young: 现在我们在 DigitalOcean 的部分谈论 SSH
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: Let's talk about SSH by
now we're in the portion of DigitalOcean
其中说，您要如何登录，可以使用 SSH 密钥或
where it says hey how do you wanna
log in you can use SSH keys or
您可以使用一次性密码。
you can use a one time password.
使用密码很容易，因为更简单的是向您发送电子邮件，
And it's tempting to use a password
because it's simpler that is email to you,
你登录你会很高兴你只会好好想想
you log in you're good to
go you only think about it.
但是我们要使用 SSH 密钥。
But we want to use an SSH key.
>> Jem Young: 这一点是关于安全的。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: And
this a whole bit on security.
安全是非常重要的。
And security is really important.
但我要告诉你安全的基本两方面
But what I'll tell you about
security there is basic two ways
如果您正在保护自己的 SSH 密钥，那么将进入服务器。
of getting into a server if you're
securing something their SSH keys.
还有用户名和密码
And there's username and password.
SSH 代表安全套接字 Shell，它是一个，好，我很快就会到达它。
SSH stands for Secure Socket Shell,
it is a, well, I'll get to it in a minute.
但它是一个非常大的关键，现在是不可突破的。
But it's a very large key that
is as of now unbreakable.
因此，它是登录服务器的一种非常安全的方法。
And so it's a much secure way
of logging into your server.
开关是由两部分组成的
The switch is made up of two parts,
that's why it's usually, for
我们都是关键的一对但我只能叫它钥匙
all us, a key pair but
I'll just call it key.
有一个公用钥匙有一个私人钥匙
There's a public key
There's a private key.
而作品的方式是
And the way that works is
私人钥匙在你的手机上留在你的电脑上
the private key stays on your computer on
your phone wherever you wanna keep it.
公用密钥在服务器上。
The public key goes on a server.
一切都是用私人钥匙加密的
And what happens is everything is
encrypted with the private key.
所以当它被加密时它会被传送到
So when it's encrypted,
it goes in transit, and
没人能拦截到底发生了什么
no one can intercept what's happening.
这其实叫隧道或管道，如果你愿意的话，
That's actually called a tunnel or a pipe,
if you will, because everything when you
建立连接，管道中的所有东西都是最不易碎的。
establish that connection, everything in
the pipe is unbreakable for the most part.
我在警告中说一切因为如果国家安全局想来找你
I say everything in caveats because
if the NSA wants to come after you,
他们会找到你的
they're gonna get you.
[ LAUGH] 世界上所有 SSH 密钥都不会保存您。
[LAUGH] All the SSH keys in
the world won't save you.
但是通常， SSH 密钥不是一般的。
But generally, SSH keys are not generally.
SSH 密钥是我们现在可以获得的最强认证。
SSH keys are the strongest
authentication we can get right now.
真的，我喜欢使用 SSH 密钥的想法，因为它只是一个真正的
And it's such a really, I like the idea
of SSH keys because it's just a really
强大的概念，我可以加密一些东西，或者你可以加密一些东西，
powerful concept, where I encrypt
something, or you can encrypt something,
而解密它的唯一方法就是用我的钥匙
and the only way to decrypt it
is with a key that only I have.
因此，您可以使用我的公用密钥向我发送一条消息。
So you can send me a message
using my public key.
任何一个人都能得到的只有你能得到的
And the only way that any and anybody can
get it you can get that you'll just get
就像一个短信的微博什么都没说
like a blob of text that means nothing.
但解密它的唯一方法是我的私人钥匙
But the only way to decrypt
it was my private key.
所以就好像是个好的加密方法
So it's like it's a good
one way encryption where
你不用相信我
you don't have to trust me.
你不需要了解我
You don't have to know me.
你只要加密它我就能解密它了
You just encrypt it, and I can decrypt it.
我是唯一一个能拦截它的人
I'm the only one and
anybody can intercept it in transit and
对他们来说不是什么意思
won't mean anything to them.
这真是一个很有才华的系统
It's really a brilliant system
that we kind of take for
那是很简单的，还是其他的选择呢 ?
granted that's really simple,
versus what are the alternatives?
用户名和密码，其中我需要知道用户名和密码
User name and password,
where I need to know a username and
我需要知道密码
I need to know a password.
如果有人窃取用户名和密码，我必须重置所有内容。
And if someone steals that username and
password I have to reset everything.
在某个时候我需要在管道上传输用户名和密码
And at some point I need the transmit that
username and password over the pipe, and
如果有人坐在中间他们可以拦截
if someone's sitting in the middle,
they can intercept that.
他们是很酷的
And they're like, cool.
您的用户名密码与专用密钥的 SSH 密钥相同
I got your username password versus
SSH key that the private key
永远不会离开我的电脑从不离开网络
never leaves my computer and
never leaves the network.
因此，您可以向我发送您想要的所有数据。
So you can send me all the data you want.
他们可以是中间的人，也可以是中间的人，
They can be a person in the middle,
aka man in the middle,
拦截你的交通
intercepting all your traffic.
这意味着 " 圣战" 。
And it means jibberish.
与使用用户名密码相比。
versus using a username password.
这就是我们使用 SSH 密钥的原因。
That's why we're using SSH keys.